into the win last time that aided the
Viking touchdown drive. Pressure coming
and it's blocked right at the 30 yd
line. The block BY ADAM AND FOR THE
touchdown Vikings
just unblocked because of the movement
of the other two guys. He's straight
into the ball. What a good play. Get up
with the ball. He gets a little block
from 54 there and stumbles in for a big
>> first down and through the air again
going deep AND WIDE OPEN IS THAILAND FOR
THE TOUCHDOWN.
[cheering]
Just a couple of minutes gone by in this
first quarter. This is Bradford's going
to take a shot. HE'S GOT HIS MAN WIDE
OPEN. It's Felen for the Minnesota
touchdown.
36 yd for Bradford. Adam Thelen at the
top of your picture comes in motion.
>> Third and goal and they go to Thelen and
Thelen will score.
Tight formation with the exception of
short-handed.
Bradford to the end zone. Felen
incomplete.
And Felen looked awfully close to being
good if he hung on. catch
two feet and if he hangs on that's a
touchdown
and the Vikings are going to challenge
the call and it looks like this will be
a touchdown. What a catch.
>> Yeah, it was an outstanding catch.
Really a perfectly thrown ball by Sam
Bradford. They come and press back
>> saying put the focus on me. I see we're
going to run the table.
He likes the way the team has responded.
Here's the goodbye. Touchdown. No flags
and the Vikings keeping pace.
How about the day for Adam Thelen
against Quinton Rollins and they get
Bradford on the edge and you see Rollins
he then bites it and Thelen is y this
game to the Packers 348.
Bradford end zone for the touchdown and
it's Thelen again. [cheering]
>> Then works that back line and with this
reception he has over 200 yds receiving
for the afternoon.
It's a great performance that's going
>> looking throwing in THE BACK OF THE END
ZONE. TOUCHDOWN. Felen
Rudolph in motion.
Pressure from Carrian. Steps away. Fires
on the run. It is caught. Unbelievable.
It's like glue on his hands from Thelen.
>> Well, earlier this year, we saw a duck
duck gray goose. Got to get it right in
Minnesota. But watch the hands. The
hands of Adam Thelen. Watch the gloves.
Look at him just snatch that one. Strong
hands. Takes
showing blitz. Rams bring it. Keenum
gets rid of it. Thelen makes the move.
Oh, [cheering] the
up to the races. [cheering]
Touchdown.
You see here again, Hatfield. He's soft
feeling. the guy who comes up with the
big plays every time you get if you see
it from the
>> Carolina playing soft again. Cover two
down the middle. THEN THE BREAKS THE
TACKLE INSIDE THE 20. ADAMS IS THE ONLY
GUY. NOPE. THAN TAKES IT for the
touchdown. Wow.
They're playing soft. They're playing
cover two
and he throws it right down the seam.
Then what a throw by Keelman.
>> Cousins pressure hit as he throws. Going
for Thelen. He's got it. WAITING FOR A
SINGLE TOUCHDOWN.
Oh my.
>> Supreme concentration by Adam Thielen.
And this is definitely a touchdown to
me. Possesses it all the way through and
he is into the end zone.
>> Second down and four. LITTLE SHOULDER
FAKE. HERE'S THELEN WIDE OPEN. THELEN
TOUCHDOWN MINNESOTA. It hurts the Eagles
helps the Vikings. Second down and two
as it took a sack off the board. Now
Phelin in the end ZONE WITH A FLAG FOR
THE TOUCHDOWN BY RONALD DERBY. And the a
good move there. There's the
>> holding number 21 defense. Fley's
declined. Touchdown.
>> Adam Theland is just special.
>> Cousins waiting. Throw it to the ENDS OF
THE CEILING. TOUCHDOWN.
JOHNSON, Marcus May, and Buster Screen
all out in the secondary. And they're
looking for the big one. And it is a
touchdown to who else but Adam Fielding.
Ton of time in a three-possession game.
Cousins puts it caught. Touchdown. Then
it
down the field they go. They go 75
into the end zone. That is a
touchdown for Adam Kel.
Mavius Murray is the running back.
Take the H. Cousins rolling chased by
Matthews fired. There'll be a first down
AND MORE AND STEEL. CAN HE GET IN? Screw
him which got the open. You can see they
had no choice there. They had to come up
and attack him and then it was Thielen
just sticking the thing in the end zone.
But it was the aggressive nature of what
Kurt Cousins was doing on the edge out
there that set that play.
[cheering]
>> Looking right all the way. HERE'S
STEELING. HIS FIRST CATCH IS A
TOUCHDOWN.
>> Second down and 12. Good for protection.
And there is Thelen. He is into the end
zone.
>> But right there, they're allowing
contact. Thelen wins one-on-one. And we
know when he catches the ball, he's
close to the end zone. Adam Thielen
usually finds.
>> And now a first down at the 35 of the
Raiders. Play fake. And on the roll out,
Cousins looking and wide open is Thielen
AND HE'LL SCORE for the Vikings on the
opening possession.
At the one
and the inside hand off to Thelen who
scores the touchdown. Adam Thelen with
his second touchdown of the game.
>> Been just m basically running this pitch
play. But I want you to watch Joseph's
eyes. He's got his eyes right here. And
who do we get? We sneak feeling right
here. He's just not ready to make the
tackle when that comes out. So there he
is. He's looking at the back field. Oop
two yd line.
There's third and four. Cousins with
TIME INTO THE END ZONE FOR THE scrimmage
and created plenty of separation. What a
good job by Kurt Cousins. Did you notice
how he was looking to your left if
you're sitting at home watching it and
then came back to your right? He held
the safeties by looking the opposite way
and came back and gave it to an open
Adam Felen. And these Vikings when they
do celebrations, they work on them.
[laughter]
>> Guard man, I love to get downfield and
run over those DBs.
>> Vikings have put up some big plays.
HERE'S COUSINS TO THE END ZONE. FELEN
WITH THE CATCH. TOUCHDOWN.
>> Felen as well because look where he put
the football. DeAndre Baker's down low
trying to make a play. And look at him
catch it. The knees are down in the end
zone.
>> Loss of a yard. Two tight ends set on
second and goal. Cousins to the end
zone. Then [cheering]
>> touchdown
in the back field. Alexander Madison in
motion.
They fake the give to Madison.
Cousins from the end zone. Is it caught?
Yes. And what a catch.
>> Toe drag. Let's see. There's the catch.
Left foot down, right foot drag, and he
completes the process.
>> Cousins for the end zone. HE'S GOT
FELEN. THELEN HAULS IT IN FOR A VIKING
TOUCHDOWN.
>> TRUSTED his speed a little bit that he
could compensate, but Felen's nifty man
and he gets behind you.
Felen in the end zone has a touchdown
Minnesota.
>> When Kurt Cousins does his job and puts
it in the position like that, they can
be very very electric
>> on this drive. He's five or five for 60
yds. Looking for more in the air. Buying
time. Cousins chased by Simmons. Throws
end zone for Thelen. HE'S GOT IT.
TOUCHDOWN. FELEN WAS ABLE to get open in
the end zone.
And Jonathan Joseph has him covered. But
Adam Thelen just like I mentioned in the
open.
[cheering]
>> Fake to Madison. Cousins fires for the
end zone. There's a flag down, but the
catch is made.
>> Good job again of just giving Kirk
enough space in that pocket. One-on-one
matchup. Big body gets in.
>> They've gone 74 yds. It's a first and
goal. Fake bootleg right throws. Caught.
Touchdown. They got back to who they are
here, which is all right, let's bootleg.
Let's roll out. Let's get Thelen working
a little on the edge
>> right out of Mississippi State. Second
down and goal.
>> Fake toss. Cousins to the end zone.
Caughten
takes it in for the touchdown.
Another great drive.
That was airda's first rushing attempt
of the season. And now Cousins going to
the air. And there is Adam.
>> As he crosses Dion Jones, he's just
going to get vertical. Now he's going to
go up
>> already in field goal range.
>> Cousins forgetting ABOUT THE FIELD GOAL.
FEEL IT. ONEARMED ABLE TO BRING IT.
>> JUST MAKES A GREAT one-handed catch. I
mean, that right there is about as good
as it gets.
>> I mean, that's that's who they look for.
or Kirk Cousins has thrown 23 touchdowns
to Adam Thielen in their time together.
Adam Thielen already has a touchdown in
this game. This is his area of the
field. Going to find him. He's matched
up right here at the bottom of the
screen. Can still get a first down on
third and four.
COUSINS THROWING AND IT IS CAUGHT.
TOUCHDOWN.
>> HE JUST follows Jordan Justin Jefferson
up there. That creates a little
indecision on the part. Now third and
goal. Ninth play of the drive. Cousins
to the end zone. There is a flag. Did he
get his feet? CATCH WAS MADE BY FELEN.
IT'S RULED A TOUCHDOWN.
>> WOW. One hand working on Anthony Brown.
One hand drags the feet.
>> First and goal from the Cowboys three
off the fake to Cousins to the end zone.
Touchdown.
Second of the game for Adam Thielen.
11th on the season.
He is slotted right
>> back of the end zone. Feling a
circuitous route for the touchdown and
another red zone score for Adam.
Allow him to run across the coverage.
Kurt Cousins was watching him the entire
way and two shots to get it in and they
have to be thinking going on fourth if
they don't get it here. BUT NOT A
PROBLEM. TOUCHDOWN TOSS FROM COUSINS TO
ADAM THIEL. HE BURNS the Bears again in
the end.
>> That was almost where I went.
>> Fourth down and goal. Cousins out to his
right. Throws pass caught, but touchdown
Phale Jenkins is pleading his walk us
through the mechanics of this.
>> Yeah, we're just looking at what where
is the ball when he first is touched by
the defender. He's airborne. Then he
comes back into the field in play,
completes the catch. So here you have
where is he first touched when that ball
does break the plane and it's
>> pretty good look there it's a touchdown
after the play
>> thought they had backed up Cousins
meanwhile Cousins throws touchdown
Vikings
Adam
>> just one-on-one on the outside
man-to-man coverage push up you get the
separation run into Eli Apple have
enough possessions left in the game
>> pressure BLITZ OPEN FIRST DOWN AND MAYBE
MORE. IT'S FEELING FOR THE TOUCHDOWN.
>> SECOND AND goal of the seven.
>> Cousins in the end zone. Touchdown.
Guess who?
Felix.
And you said it partner. In the red
zone. This young man is money.
So now third and 13 for Minnesota at the
15 of Seattle.
>> Cousins steps away from pressure to the
END ZONE. IT'S THELEN FOR THE TOUCHDOWN.
>> WATCH THIS all 22. They're going to use
this post inside to gobble up the
safety. Here comes Adam Thielen on the
outside post. And Kirk Cousins, he's
going to stare that safety down. He's
saying, "Hey, take the cheese down the
middle of the field. I'm going to let
out."
>> Now Justin Jefferson one-on-one with
Dante Jackson.
Cousins on third down throws to the end
zone. TOUCHDOWN.
ADAM THELEN MAKES THE catch and the
Vikings
extend their lead. Two touchdowns in
under a minute for Minnesota.
>> Let the Jones family McCarthy the
training staff.
>> Second and 11. Cousins meanwhile with
that pump fake fires a little wide open
is stealing for the touchdown.
>> [cheering]
>> Cousins throwing the fade FOR THELEN. IT
IS CAUGHT FOR THE TOUCHDOWN. [cheering]
>> And Thelen right here. They're They're
looking for
No, I don't think there's a push off
there. I don't think the arms [cheering]
fourman rush again. Cousins gets rid of
it. FEL MAKES A MOVE AND HE'S IN FOR THE
TOUCHDOWN.
>> Justin Jefferson.
Play action. Cousins throws end zone.
TOUCHDOWN.
Adam Thelen. Watch Adam Thelen. He's
been so smooth. You see, he finds the
hole in the zone and then just keeps
climbing. That's the beauty of this
route. You keep climbing so that only
you can get that throw or it's going to
>> suck it down at three. Off the play
fake. Cousins sets, throws, END ZONE,
DIVING CATCH, TOUCHDOWN,
second of the game, Adam Thielen.
>> What a communication between Kurt
Cousins and Adam Thielen. They both
ready at the same time. Thelen's just,
you see him jogging and THEN JUST SHOOTS
RIGHT up the middle of the field.
>> So it sets the Vikings up here trying to
break that goose egg. Cousins fakes the
toss and back TO THE END ZONE. Wide
open. There he is. Adam Thielen his 50th
career touchdown reception
on second down. Cousins look right left
now throws up the middle AND THE CATCH
IS MADE FOR A TOUCHDOWN BY ADAM.
Now this time let's give credit to the
offensive line because this was a very
very slow developing play. Kirk Cousins
really wanted to catch it and to deal
with coverage.
And the Vikings are the beneficiaries.
Cousins looking Jefferson was covered.
OTHER SIDE FEELING AN OLD TIME PLAY.
It's a double crisscross against man
coverage. Plenty of time.
>> Fourth down and four.
Here's Cousins near side. THEN FIRST
DOWN TOUCHDOWN.
So Okonnell's DECISION PAYS off as
Cousins connects with Thelen from 23 yds
out on fourth down. more maybe
one-on-one coverage.
>> Play action for Cousins. LOOKING END
ZONE OPEN. TOUCHDOWN. ADAM THELAND.
DONE.
>> You're right about that. A little slow
play. They play action. Adam Thelen
crashes down as if he's blocking late.
>> First and goal. Four yd line. FAKE TO
COOK. COUSINS. END ZONE. TOUCHDOWN. ADAM
THELEN.
>> They're stealing. You bunch them all in.
You think that they're going to block
Galvin Cook in the back field and as
soon as they take their eyes off of that
looking at Dvin Cook